

about me

Hi, I'm Pedro Gomes born in Madeira Island, Portugal. Driven by a lifelong passion for technology, I taught myself how to code from an early age, later going on to study and learn everything related to multimedia creation and production. Throughout the years I have gained some experience from volunteering in small companies during academic breaks and part-time jobs in larger companies where I collaborated / carried out projects and works in the area of Design and Multimedia. I also attended some complementary courses in Photoshop, Illustrator and 3D Studio Max.

Having completed my education and worked on several independent projects, I now feel able to take on any challenge, whether it's video production, broadcasting, photography, web development, programming or design.



+351 968 213 911



pedrofacg@gmail.com



http://pgmulti.media

experience

Rugby AAC Multimedia Producer

2014-2017 Creator and manager of every media content in Rugby AAC Club during this period.

Created social media posters, a wide range of videos (promotional, presentations, motivational, etc.), recording of training sessions for analysis and live stream of games.

Estudio 21 Multimedia Producer

2013 Developed a new website for this sub-company of EMLI Music Group and all graphic

elements for it's grand opening event.

EMLI Music Group Graphic Designer

2011 - 2013 Designed various graphic elements to update the store image.

education

ISMT

2012 - 2017

Multimedia

Completed bachelor degree in Instituto Superior Miguel Torga (Coimbra).

Students are empowered to exercise the various new professions which guarantee the harmonious relationship between the fields of Communications, Information Technology and Design.

- Web designer.
- Managers of projects in the area of information systems, specifically in the production and editing multimedia (internet, digital media, online publications, ...).
- Director graphics and image production.
- Centers of Computer and Audiovisual Media.
- Departments of image editing and sound in audiovisual production companies.
- Departments of graphic design for screen (including TV and video).
- Creative departments in advertising companies.
- Centers of Computer and Audiovisual Media.
- E-learning.
- Multimedia Teaching.
- Multimedia Communication.

skills

I consider myself a committed, hardworking person with good ability to meet deadlines and an enormous desire to continue learning and developing my skills.

IMAGE	VIDEO	SOUND	3D	PROGRAMMING
Photoshop	Premiere	Audition	Unity 3D	HTML
Lightroom	After Effects	Ableton	3D Studio Max	CSS
Illustrator	Resolve		Cinema 4D	JS / jQuery
	Final Cut			MongoDB / MySQL
				Node.js
				React
				Java
				C#

languages

Portuguese 100%

English

more info



Immediate availability

90%